<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>VegSja&#39;s Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/</link>
    <description>Recent content on VegSja&#39;s Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.146.5</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 20:51:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I created a landing page in 30 minutes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/articles/how-i-created-a-landing-page-in-30-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 20:51:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/articles/how-i-created-a-landing-page-in-30-minutes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a developer working on a new backcountry skiing app, I faced the challenge of quickly creating a landing page to introduce the product and start building a community. My app, designed to help skiers navigate the Norwegian mountains safely, isn’t ready yet, but I wanted to have something live that would allow people to sign up for a waitlist and get excited about the upcoming launch. With everything else going on, I needed to get the landing page up and running in the quickest, most efficient way possible—ideally within 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/vegsja-home/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-hey-im-vegard-sjåvik&#34;&gt;👋 Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Vegard Sjåvik&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a computer science graduate from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ntnu.no/&#34;&gt;NTNU&lt;/a&gt; (class of 2025), where I specialized in Artificial Intelligence 🤖. My academic journey focused on how machines can learn, adapt, and support humans—particularly through building solid training data foundations for robust machine learning models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, I’ve developed a broad skill set across the stack—from frontend and backend development to infrastructure and DevOps. I&amp;rsquo;m especially passionate about the role data plays in modern software. My focus spans the full data lifecycle: from collection and processing to enabling data-driven decisions and powering advanced AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
